### Pat Mifsud

patmifsud@me.com Sydney, Australia Folio: patmifsud.com 0448 742 570

# I'm a passionate designer specialising in user interfaces and user experience research.

I believe that great design is visually appealing, solves the right problem for the right person, and is feasible to build.

#### **Experience**

#### UI / UX Designer at The Big Crunch Feb 2019 - Now

I designed interfaces for web and mobile productivity tools, testing both prototypes and mvp builds. I ran over 40 user tests and interviews for less then \$300. We grew our userbase from two to four figures. I created a basic design system for the company in Figma where stakeholders and developers could directly collaborate on designs.

I swapped hats to design/ growth hacking/ front end development/ customer support as needed.

#### CX Designer at Ailo Sep 2018 - Dec 2018

I worked across disciplines and teams to design and build scalable systems to convert trials to subscriptions and decrease churn.

I designed and built onboarding campaigns and landing pages with the CX team, working with the backend systems (Mailchimp/ Vero) that drove them.

I designed dashboards and reports to keep sales and engineering teams in touch with their impact on the customer experience through Salesforce and external tools.

#### Product Owner at LPMA (Owned by Ailo) Feb 2018 - Sep 2018

I worked with domain experts, stakeholders, internal and external engineering and design teams to own and design a business consulting product.

I worked with an external development company to build consulting products and client resources.

## Graphic / UX Designer at Apmasphere (Owned by Ailo) Feb 2017 - Feb 2018

I created prototypes and ran usability testing sessions, presenting results to design team, developers and stakeholders.

I learned Framer.js to allow us to prototype complex interactions and animations, validated and iterated on these designs through user feedback.

## **Graphic Designer** at I-MANIFEST Charity 2014 - 2015

Graphic and web designer, probono.

#### Designer and Marketing Coordinator at Apmasphere (Owned by Ailo) Mar 2015 - Feb 2017

I worked on branding, print and digital design work, video and animation projects, email marketing, physical spaces - designing conference booths, signage and branding.

#### Graphic Designer at Urban Purveyor Group 2013 - 2015 (Saké, Löwenbräu, The Argyle)

#### Assistant Teacher at UTS Sydney Feb - May 2014

#### **Education**

#### Bachelor of Design in Visual Communication -University of Technology Sydney

**Distinction Averge.** I took electives in user experience, animation and frontend programming.

## Certificate IV in Graphic Design & Communication WSI, NADC (TAFE)

#### Folio and case studies: patmifsud.com Referees on request